Icefall is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Stefan Ruzowitzky.
A young Indigenous game warden arrests an infamous poacher only to discover that the poacher knows the
location of a plane carrying millions of dollars that has crashed in a frozen lake.
When a group of criminals and dirty cops are alerted to the poacher’s whereabouts, the warden and the
poacher team up to fight back and escape across the treacherous lake before the ice melts.
Harlan, played by Joel Kinnaman.
Ani, played by Cara Jade Myers.
Rhodes, played by Danny Huston.
Oz, played by Graham Greene.
Pen, played by Martin Sensmeier.
Dax, played by Oliver Trevena.
Icefall is a 2025 American thriller film directed by Stefan
Ruzowitzky and written by George Mahaffey and Steve Isles.
It has Joel Kinnaman and Cara Jade Myers in the lead roles.
The film was released on November 4, 2025.
The tone is intense.